Previously on
The Big Bang Theory...
Hey, Stuart.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I'm living here again.
Do, uh, Howard
and Bernadette know?
Or is it like a possum
in the walls kind of thing?
No. I needed
a place to stay,
and with the baby coming,
I figured they could
use some extra help.
Hey, tomorrow, who wants
to paint the nursery?
I'll do it.
Why do you get to do it?
I'm the artist.
Just because you're starving
doesn't make you an artist.
Just because I look sickly
doesn't mean I'm starving.
Howard?
I think I'm in labor.
Oh. Oh, okay. Okay.
Uh, uh, uh,
I can do this.
We have a plan.
Somebody please
tell me the plan!
I'll get the
hospital bag.
I'll pull the van up.
Meet you outside
in two minutes.
Team Baby, go!
Oh, man.
(Howard:)This is really
happening.
(Howard:)You doin' okay?
(Bernadette:)Here comes another contraction.
Let's pick it up!
(Raj:)All right, hold on.
(Raj:)I'm gonna drive
like we do in India.
(Raj:)Get out of my way,
you syphilitic dogs!
Stop that!
This isn't India.
(Raj:)Fine.
(Raj:)What do one point three billion
people know about having babies?
(Howard:)Sorry. I know you were just
trying to help.
(Howard:)I love you.
(Raj:)I love you, too.
We're good.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪